<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<testimonials>
  <client>
    <documentary>Chukker - Around Polo</documentary>
    <content>An outstanding piece of research put together by a connoisseur and a lover of the sport. Yasmin, super show and very well done.</content>
    <name>Colonel JS Virk</name>
    <designation>Honorary Secretary, Indian Polo Association</designation>
    <date>May, 2007</date>
  </client>
  <client>
    <documentary>Chukker - Around Polo</documentary>
    <content>An aesthetically made film traces the origin of Polo and highlights most lucidly the role of the Army in keeping the noble game alive.</content>
    <name>Lt. Gen. Sudhir Sharma (AVSM,YSM, VSM)</name>
    <designation>QMG and Army Chief Steward, Indian Polo Association</designation>
    <date>June, 2007</date>
  </client>
  <client>
    <documentary>Destination MP</documentary>
    <content>an excellent film produced by Yasmin Kidwai,  on a subject not very visually conducive. Ms. Kidwai did an excellent job and produced very interesting film capturing the essence of the subject. The film has more than served its purpose and has been utilized for projecting the highways and road development work being done in MP. It has been extensively used by us in various national and international seminars and presentations</content>
    <name>Mohd. Suleman</name>
    <designation>Managing Director and Ex-officio secretary, PWD. Govt. of Madhya Pradesh.</designation>
    <date>December, 2009</date>
  </client>
  <client>
    <documentary>Get Set Go</documentary>
    <content>An insightful, entertaining documentary that makes one appreciate our country. </content>
    <name>Priya Dutt</name>
    <designation>MP Lok Sabha</designation>
    <date>May, 2010</date>
  </client>
  <client>
    <documentary>25 years of Hope</documentary>
    <content>A film that shows how the human spirit has risen above the ordinary to overcome the great tragedy.- SR Mohant, Secretary, Public health and Family Welfare, Bhopal Gas Tragedy Relief and Rehabilitation Department, Govt. of Madhya Pradesh.</content>
    <name>SR Mohanty</name>
    <designation>Secretary, Govt. of Madhya Pradesh</designation>
    <date>February, 2010</date>
  </client>
  <client>
    <documentary>where do I go from here</documentary>
    <content>scenes were so moving and depicted with such sensitivity that at the end I felt a lump in my throat. The direction and editing shows a maturity, I must say, I did not expect from a young film maker like yourself, Yasmin. It was far beyond your years.</content>
    <name>Khalid R.</name>
    <designation>Social activist, Bhopal</designation>
    <date>March, 2003</date>
  </client>
  <client>
    <documentary>Call of the Wild</documentary>
    <content>A bench mark in Eco Tourism Films</content>
    <name>AK Varma</name>
    <designation>Managing Director, Karnataka State Forest Industries Corpn. Limited.</designation>
    <date>April, 2010</date>
  </client>
  <client>
    <documentary>Borders and Beyond</documentary>
    <content>It was pleasant to view your  bold attempt, Borders and Beyond…The documentary deserves to go a long way- opening eyes  of “preset-notioned-mind”</content>
    <name>VK Naswa</name>
    <designation>Social activist, Bhopal</designation>
    <date>November, 2002</date>
  </client>
  <client>
    <documentary>GMR films</documentary>
    <content>The films have served their purpose and have been utilized for projecting the environmental policies and safety procedures at the airport. We would highly recommend M/S Spring Box Films for their focus on content and high production values and value given to client satisfaction</content>
    <name>Saptarishi Sanyal</name>
    <designation>Head- corporate communications, Delhi International Airport (P) Ltd.</designation>
    <date>July, 2014</date>
  </client>
</testimonials>
